hi my name is Joe Brewer and I'm the
director of cognitive policy works and I
need your help right now the progressive
movement in the United States is in
serious trouble we have in our midst a
set of global challenges that are
putting the future of our country at
risk we have things like global warming
or the global economy that's become
unstable and we have some serious
challenges before us yet our politics is
totally inadequate to the task what we
saw in this year's election was a
reduction to the lowest common
denominator we saw manipulations and
smears used to set the agenda we saw
lies and deception used to create clouds
of smoke and mirrors that are keeping us
from dealing with real threats like
global warming or like the tremendous
inequalities in wealth or like the loss
of basic health services that people are
experiencing an economic downturn and
through the manipulative practices of
insurance companies so my colleagues and
I a cognitive policy works have a
proposition for you we would like to
create the progressive strategy handbook
and with this booklet we would create a
framework for strategic action to help
guide the movement as we dress address
the root causes of these problems and
others in order to do this we're asking
for your help we want to raise five
thousand dollars and then myself my
colleagues sarah robinson in erica's
will come together and write a handbook
that will publish at the end of the year
and then give away free of charge on our
website to help progressives everywhere
some of the things that will cover in
this handbook are the importance of
framing and how it works so that
progressives can help tackle
conservative arguments and beat them
down point out the absurdities and what
the opposition is doing but also dig
deeper into the global trends that are
causing rapid shifts in the way that our
country Orient's itself in the world and
how we address the threats that are
before us so will you help us